What?
Make sure they will be there later, okay?
Siloy's wife said
she'd meet you at the morgue.
- Morgue?
- She said Siloy's dead.
Siloy!
- Son of a...
- Are you going to tell us the truth?
Or should I bring your young daughter here?
Leave my daughter out of it!
Even the best film has an ending.
Not all can be done with magic.
Your dad collapsed in his house!
I'm sorry, my dear.
- I thought you quit already?
- What matters is you're safe.
Get well, okay?
- Do you want to see her?
- I'm busy here.
- I've got work to do.
- Hey.
Go.
Are you just going to let him go, Miss?
I also want to make sure
if he still knows his way back home.
Liam.
Vergil.
What is Vergil doing here?
You and your sons are testing my patience.
Danilo, it was Liam who approached me.
He said he needed money
for his mom's operation.
And because he is Via's boyfriend,
I let him join my business.
And now you're going to tag Vergil along?
- You are like leeches.
- Uncle!
Uncle...
Kneel down when you're talking to him.
Dad didn't know I followed him.
Punish me instead.
Vergil, stay out of this.
What do you know about this business?
Uncle, this isn't new to me.
I'm now a part of it.
But please, not my dad.
Let him work at Casa Fuerte.
I can be your right-hand man.
Big bro, what do I do with these two?
He said he wanted to be my right-hand man.
Give it a try.
Uncle!
Thank you, Uncle Ramon.
I won't disappoint you.
You heard Uncle Ramon, right?
I'm now his right-hand man.
Help me get up.
Give me your right hand.
He said right hand, right?
Hey!
Don't hurt him!
That's enough!
If only Joyce had listened to me,
you now would've been her boyfriend.
- Auntie...
- Mommy.
I'm not in a rush.
I'm being a workaholic like her.
Gosh.
With the money you make
and your family's business,
you can ask Joyce to quit acting. Right?
Mommy, please, just eat.
I'm on a diet.
This is what I only eat.
Hey.
I'm waiting for an important email. Hey!
Joyce.
Finally, we already have a lead
to help with the investigation.
The CCTV captured a man
when the crime happened, Auntie.
That's not a good topic in the morning.
It's not office hours yet.
Look at the time.
There are still two minutes left.
Eat.
Eat first.
Look at that. Look at your cell phones.
Matchy-matchy. A match made in heaven.
Unlike Edmond and I.
It's like dealing with a demon.
Mommy.
Hello?
Jana, good morning.
So?
There's no news
about Joyce's junkie father, right?
That's good to hear.
I'm glad.
Thank you for the breakfast.
Two minutes are over.
You can't leave until you finish your food.
Eat.
Your suit will get stains.
- Go on. You can leave now.
- Please.
Go.
- I only have a little leftover.
- Water.
- Okay?
- Okay.
Thank you, Auntie.
Thank you for the breakfast.
Bye.
Just be patient with my daughter.
She'll say yes eventually.
Mom...
I hope so.
How are you doing, Dad?
I'm great.
Our new counselor is good.
He's the one who encouraged me to...
How should I say this?
Dear...
I want to tell you why I always return to...
- to my old ways...
- Go ahead, Dad.
I'll listen.
Well, this is what happened.
I met some people before.
Who is this?
Hello?
Hello, sorry I can't take calls right now.
Attorney Hans, I sent you the video.
I had it enhanced too.
Attorney Hans?
You can already see
the suspect's face on that copy.
This is Joyce.
Joyce? Why do you have Hans' phone?
Hello?
Jayps?
We switched our phones.
I'm sorry. I'll bring his phone
to your office.
I'll tell him to find you when he gets here.
Okay, thank you.
- Vergil.
- You, monster!
Who is that?
Someone sent a video.
He's the suspect in the case
that Hans is investigating.
Wait.
I know that man.
He finally admitted it.
Do you know him, Dad?
Dad, wait. How do you know this man?
Dad, what is it that you're going to tell me?
Tell you?
I'll tell you next time.
Dear, listen carefully.
Don't get involved in Hans' investigation.
They're dangerous.
Okay?
You better do this.
- Dad...
- Warn Hans.
Tell him to stop the investigation.
- Okay?
- I don't get you, Dad.
You'll get hurt.
What's going on with you, Dad?
Listen to me, Joyce.
I don't understand.
- It's an order. No, no.
- Sir, that's enough.
Hold on.
Wait!
I'm protecting my daughter.
Dad, hold on.
Wait a minute.
Ma'am, we'll let him rest for now.
Rest? What rest?
I don't need rest.
I'm her father.
- Come on, let's go.
- I will protect her.
Listen to me, Joyce.
Do as I say.
Stay away from those demons.
Joyce!
My child!
They are demons!
Calm down, you two.
Vergil, why are you hurting your brother?
Why do you have an arm sling?
What's happening?
Mom, can you leave us alone for now?
We need to talk.
No.
I won't go anywhere.
I'm your mom.
I have the right to know
what's going on with the two of you.
Vergil, I know you don't like me.
But I never stopped being concerned
about you.
You can ask Liam if you want.
Now I want to know what trouble you have.
What do you mean by
what you said earlier, Vergil?
What did Liam do to Danilo?
Come on. What's going on?
I'm sorry, Aunt Tess.
I lost my patience when I found out that...
I found out that Liam left a huge debt
in Casa Fuerte.
Dad told me.
And now he's paying for it.
Is that so?
So, it's your fault, son.
And I'm blaming your brother.
Son, fix that problem.
You should pay your father.
That's embarrassing.
Oh, dear. Talk to each other decently.
I'm going to leave you here.
No fighting.
Yes, Mom.
Thank you.
Thank you for keeping the truth from my mom.
Can we talk somewhere else?
Thank you.
We switched our phones.
Hello.
What's with the video that was sent to you?
Video? What video?
The video you're waiting for from Jayps.
My dad saw the man in the video.
And he knows him.
He knows him?
That's good, Joyce.
Where's Uncle Edmond? Can I talk to him?
Because it will make my investigation easier.
- Come on, let's see him.
- You can't talk to him, Hans.
You know his condition.
You can't do that.
I'll find the right time.
I'll try to ask him.
I'm sorry, Joyce.
Maybe he's the key
to giving my client justice.
If there's someone who has to pay
for what happened.
You don't know how big this case is.
Stay away from those demons!
They're evil, Joyce!
My child!
They are demons!
See what you did?
Dad is paying for your mistakes.
Dad is now managing
Uncle Ramon's transactions.
The job you left.
Transactions?
Uncle Ramon's illegal money.
Drugs, gambling dens, illegal weapons.
He puts all the money in Casa Fuerte
to launder it.
Money laundering?
You know what, Liam?
You're the dumbest in the family.
You have nothing to brag about.
I'll do everything to get you and dad
out of this trouble.
- I'll talk to Uncle Ramon.
- It's too late.
Dad and I already know a lot.
But you...
Uncle Ramon let you go because of Via.
So fix your life.
And stay with Via.
Because the moment you break up with her,
you'll be dead.
And so will everyone who matters to you.
Do you understand?
End whatever's going on
between you and Joyce.
Bro...
I grew up getting mad
whenever you'd call me brother.
But this will be the only time
I'll be your big brother.
Get your act together.
Fix your relationship with Via.
She's the only protection you have.
My friend...
do I really have to learn this?
Yes.
So that if your sons fail...
you'll be the one to shoot them.
And if you fail...
you'll have to shoot yourself.
Come on, my friend.
I'm not kidding.
You would rather take a bullet
than suffer my punishment
if you put me in trouble, Danilo.
How's Liam?
I let him do the things he wants.
Make a movie?
He even dragged my daughter into it.
It's fine, if only he's not cheating on Via.
What do you mean?
Liam loves Via so much.
Fix my target.
Fix it.
Intoy...
What do you do
when problems keep coming your way?
Nothing.
I let the problem worry about me.
Can't you loosen up a bit?
Looks like it's serious.
Dude...
People deal with problems differently.
But most of the time,
they choose the easiest way.
Running away.
But some choose the wrong path.
Or some focus on other things.
Sometimes people lack courage...
Courage to deal with their problems.
Oftentimes, the solution is within our reach.
But we are taken over by fear.
I understand everything you told me, Intoy.
I just don't want my problems
to cause harm to others...
Especially my loved ones.
Why did you do that?
Are you going to kill me?
If you were my target,
you wouldn't be able to talk anymore.
Do you know what I told Liam?
If he goes against me,
he's not the one who will get hurt.
It's the people who matter to him.
Why?
Is it because of this?
Do you think Liam and Joyce have an affair?
It's just a film.
They don't have a relationship.
My daughter and I are not
the kind of people you can fool.
And once I confirm
that Liam is just using me
and my daughter... I'm sorry.
Your clan will end with him.
- Director Phil, everything is set.
- Okay.
Josh, Joyce, can we do it in one take?
Sure.
We always do it in one take.
Warn Hans.
Tell him to stop investigating.
- Okay?
- Dad, I can't understand.
You'll only get in trouble.
Where's Uncle Edmond?
Can I talk to him?
It will make my investigation easier.
Joyce?
Hey.
I don't think we can do it in one take.
Sorry, Director Phil. Yes.
Sorry, where were we?
We're just here.
But I don't know where you are.
You're zoning out.
Is something bothering you, Joyce?
Nothing, Josh. I'm okay.
Sir Liam, the stunt man we had last time
didn't return.
What do we do with continuity?
Sir Liam.
C-Come again?
Deedee, it's okay. I had him picked up.
Sir Liam, everything's okay.
Okay.
Are you okay, Sir Liam?
I'm okay. Don't worry about me.
Okay. I'll be right there
if you need anything.
Okay.
Coffee!
To wake you up, Boss Bro.
You seem lost.
Miss Joyce...
There.
So you can come back to earth.
Your mind is somewhere else.
Joyce...
Are you sure you can start now?
How about you? Are you ready?
Sorry.
I'm so sorry, I'm late.
Did you already start?
Someone got here at the same time I did.
Hello.
Hello, everyone.
I'm glad to be part of your movie.
Joyce, really?
We're going to work with Maxine?
Miss Lemon asked us
to include her in our project.
Isn't she the one your fans suspect
to be your online basher?
Isn't she the Girl with the Periwinkle Hair?
We don't have any concrete evidence for that.
I don't want any problems on my set.
We're going to shoot the final sequence.
It should be perfect.
Joyce.
Maxine.
- Cindy.
- I'm so tired.
Cindy.
I'm so tired.
I thought we would both find
a way to save our relationship.
- But why is this happening?
- No.
Cindy.
Sorry if you got tired.
Sorry if you feel alone.
This is what I only got.
I'm sorry if you got dragged
into my miserable life.
I will understand if you want to leave me.
Am I alone?
Am I the only one willing to fight?
I love you...
So much.
That's why I want you to be happy.
Do you think I'm happy
with what's happening to us?
I don't want to be selfish.
I don't want to have you...
and trap you in this relationship.
I know...
that I hurt you over and over again.
I'm sorry.
Love, the clothes that
Director Phil requested have arrived.
And I ordered takeout
from our favorite restaurant.
Sorry.
While I'm still perfecting
Aunt Tess' recipes,
have some of the takeout food first.
Yummy. Do you want some rice?
I'll get you some.
Let's eat, love.
Sorry, I should send this to
our film director before the break ends.
What?
We have breaks so we can eat.
Come on.
Have a break.
Here.
You know I don't eat that.
Sorry, love.
- Via.
- Go on. Try it.
I'm still full.
I'm not hungry yet.
I'll put a bigger chunk of meat.
So it will be yummier.
- Via.
- Come on, love.
I'm not hungry yet. I'm okay, promise.
I'll eat after this.
Oh, sorry.
Sorry, sorry, sorry.
I'll clean it up.
Let me.
I told you I'm not hungry yet, Via.
Why won't you just leave me be?
Liam, what else do I have to do?
Via, what is your problem?
Can you stop treating me like a child?
You're asking me what the problem is?
Asking me that stupid question?
You know we have a problem, Liam.
Can you tell me the truth?
Are you just staying with me
because you know
my dad might do something if we break up?
Via, no. What are you saying?
So do you just feel sorry for me?
Via, no.
Answer me, Liam!
I don't know anymore!
Via, I don't know anymore.
I don't know! I'm confused!
I just want to explode!
I want to explode
because this is already so full!
This is full of things I never wanted!
Like our relationship?
Via...
You showed me nothing but kindness.
So I want you to be happy.
But I don't think...
I'm the right person to make you feel that.
What?
No.
What are you saying? Wait, what?
Via, I'm sorry.
Love...
- I'm sorry.
- Liam.
[Username: TGWTPH]
[Password]
[The Girl with the Periwinkle Hair Channel]
[Upload Photos/Videos]
[Files]
Checkmate.
This.
Mate.
One more round.
And because of some unforeseen problems...
I am sad to announce that my godson,
the biggest action star of his generation,
Josh Pelaez,
is withdrawing his candidacy.
And I, your humble servant,
will continue with the fight.
Today, I am announcing my candidacy...
for senator.
[Congressman Ramon dela Peña
to run for Senator]
Ms. Joyce, I went to the laundromat.
I also asked Leroy to carry it for me.
But your clothes aren't fully dry yet.
- Should I hang it for you?
- Oh, no.
No, I can do that.
Go on. Go back to the set.
Our director might look for you.
I'll take care of this.
- Are you sure?
- Do you take a break?
Why don't you get some rest?
- Okay.
We'll go back to the set, Miss Joyce.
Leroy, Deedee.
Thank you.
Thank you for staying on in this project...
even though we had multiple setbacks.
And even though we don't have a huge budget,
you chose to stay.
Thank you.
Deedee, Leroy, you're here.
Miss Joyce, if you need anything
in your accommodation,
just let me know.
I don't need anything.
I'm thanking Leroy and Deedee.
And you, too.
Actually, I'm grateful to
the whole production team, to everyone.
Thank you.
Honestly, we, the actors, owe you a lot.
Yes, it's us that the people see.
We represent the whole team.
We're the ones who receive the praises.
But you, guys...
You are the real unsung and unseen heroes
of the production.
I'm proud to be part of this movie,
Miss Joyce.
This is my first big project.
My parents are so proud of me.
As for me...
I'm actually tired of writing movie scripts
for Congressman Ramon in Blacksmith.
It's always the same action movies
full of machismo.
But you know what?
This is the first time I felt excited again
in writing a simple but sincere
and heartfelt story.
Well, actually,
I think I gained the most in this project.
Because of you and Sir Liam,
I became passionate again in this industry.
I've always wanted to quit
because of burnout.
But whenever I see
how passionate you and Sir Liam are,
I am reminded of my old self...
Of how I used to be when I was just starting.
All I want to do are good and relevant films.
Sorry, I can't help but cry.
Thank you so much.
Seriously, thank you so much.
This film won't be possible without you.
Thank you.
After this film,
I promise, we will make more films together.
I'd love that, Miss Joyce.
Game!
Okay, I'll prepare a budget
for our future projects.
Can I have a hug?
I'm so proud of you.
Group hug.
Come on, let's go.
Miss Joyce might still have to
memorize her script.
Go on. Go back to the set.
- Hurry up.
- Bye, Miss Joyce.
We'll go ahead, Miss Joyce.
We'll get going.
- Okay.
- Bye.
(Thank you.)
Liam, are you okay?
How long have you been there?
Wait, are we going to
shoot my scenes already?
Sorry, I didn't notice you.
Joyce...
There's something I want to tell you.
What is it?
I can't help it anymore.
What?
I can't bear this anymore, Joyce.
I feel like exploding.
- Where? Which?
- Can you let me talk first?
Okay.
Joyce...
I just want to let you know that...
before we worked together...
I was at the point in my life
where I was lost.
And you...
You taught me how to find myself.
Joyce...
I don't know where I'll be without you.
Me, too, Liam.
I'm also happy to be working with you.
Wait. Where is this headed?
I love you.
I love you, Joyce.
I loved you the first time I saw you.
The first time you saw me?
A few months ago?
No.
It's been a long time.
It's been a long time, Joyce.
I have loved you for a long time.
And even though a lot has already happened
in our lives...
I still love you.
Liam, I can't...
I can't understand.
It's hard to explain.
But I love you.
Joyce...
Joyce, we're now at the hospital.
Hang in there, please.
Your dad is here too.
What did you do?
That's how I can protect myself
from Joyce's revelation.
Deep inside your heart,
that's what you want, too.
For that woman to be gone.
What happened to my daughter?
I have no one to blame but you!
What happened?
What?